<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<page>
  <title>About the Author</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;div style="text-align: center"&gt;
&lt;img style="border-image: initial; border-width: 2px; border-color: navy; border-style: solid" src="/pics/Blog_MountainView.JPG" alt="Mountain View" title="Mountain View" width="300" height="400" align="top" /&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div style="text-align: center"&gt;
&lt;div align="left"&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; I graduated from the University of Texas in Austin with a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science in 2006. There, I was humbled to learn what Computer Science was really about. During my one and only summer internship at Mary Kay Inc, I was one of the first to test drive Visual Studio 2005 code-named &amp;ldquo;Whidbey&amp;rdquo;. I got to do Unit Testing, and work on an in-house XML web application. I had a blast. I was hired by Software Architects in the summer of 2006. For a recent college grad, I have no doubt that software consulting is the very best thing you can do. There&amp;rsquo;s something prestigious about getting to work on several different technologies in such a short time, and being part of a company with a diverse mix of junior and senior developers all across the board. Software Architects has since been acquired by Sogeti USA, providing software consulting and enterprise technology solutions globally. 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p align="left"&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; In March of 2008, I received my MCPD in ASP.NET Web Application Development. I think I&amp;rsquo;ve found my passion on the web side, with an additional obsession of the user experience. That points me toward ASP.NET, MOSS 2007, and WPF / Silverlight to name the best. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align="left"&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; On December 6th 2008, I married Xuan Nguyen. Our family consists of two chihuahuas, Fluffy (male) and Cocoa Bean (female). We have an apartment in the northern part of Houston TX. In our spare time, we enjoy shopping, watching movies, and eating seafood. Yeah, she completes me. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align="left"&gt;
Contact me via email at &lt;a href="mailto:bpanjavan@alumni.cs.utexas.edu" title="bpanjavan@alumni.cs.utexas.edu"&gt;bpanjavan@alumni.cs.utexas.edu&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p align="left"&gt;
Thanks for reading. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&amp;nbsp; 
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
  <keywords>About, Author</keywords>
  <slug>About the Author</slug>
  <parent>00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000</parent>
  <isfrontpage>False</isfrontpage>
  <showinlist>True</showinlist>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <datecreated>2009-02-24 20:49:35</datecreated>
  <datemodified>2012-02-18 09:13:12</datemodified>
</page>